ladymoments.com 2013-06-04

# Lady Moments

LadyMoments.com does not reveal membership information. Confidentiality and participation in events related to, or outside of LadyMoments.com is strictly at the will of individual members.

Where this privacy policy applies

This privacy policy only applies to LadyMoments.com’s site http://www.LadyMoments.com. It does not apply to linked pages or sites connected to or co-branded with LadyMoments.com. This privacy page will be linked to any page authorized by phatGURU. By your use of LadyMoments.com and/or submission of any personal information to us, you agree to the use of your personal information according to LadyMoments.com terms and are subject to the terms of this privacy policy.

Information we collect about LadyMoments.com users

Registration information

Most of LadyMoments.com can be browsed without disclosing personal information. However, if you wish to use services offered on LadyMoments.com or obtain privileged information made available by LadyMoments.com, you may be asked contact information such as your name, email address, residential address and postcode.

Choosing not to provide requested contact information may result in not being able to use the service or obtain the information you seek. LadyMoments.com may also collect information that you provide during registration, orders, surveys, contests and promotions and other communications with us. LadyMoments.com will collect your personal information only with your knowledge and your consent.

Cookies

LadyMoments.com uses cookies in order to track your visit to LadyMoments.com. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many websites use them to provide useful features for their customers. LadyMoments.com may associate the information stored in a user’s cookie with other personal data and information that the user has provided to LadyMoments.com.

To monitor usage and to help improve the service provided to its customers, LadyMoments.com also embeds cookies from a number of third parties in the site.

How your information is used

The personal information that you disclose to LadyMoments.com may be used to provide you with goods, services and features and to communicate with you. Such information may also be used for verification purposes, fulfilling orders, prizes, tracking compliance with the terms and conditions of use for LadyMoments.com, compliance with applicable laws and the performance of legal obligations.

LadyMoments.com uses the information obtained from cookies for several purposes. The cookies enable us to understand your own personal preferences and tailor your experience on LadyMoments.com by using those preferences. LadyMoments.com also uses cookies to track user trends and patterns. The information which LadyMoments.com receives from cookies enables us to modify and improve LadyMoments.com to meet the needs of our users, including yourself.

When users provide LadyMoments.com with registration information such as name, email address and postal address, this data can be matched with cookie data, if cookies have been set to be received. This means LadyMoments.com is able to match an identifiable user with specific usage of LadyMoments.com. This information would be used by LadyMoments.com and its parent companies only.

LadyMoments.com logs IP addresses for purposes of site administration and collecting aggregate information about the visitors to LadyMoments.com.
